http://www.natureandmore.com/en/privacy-statement

Privacy Statement
Eosta/Nature&More may process personal data about you if you use the services of Eosta/Nature&More, and/or because you provide these to Eosta/Nature&More yourself when completing a contact form on the website. Eosta/Nature&More may process the following personal data:Your first and last nameYour address detailsYour phone numberYour e-mail addressYour IP address
WHY DO WE NEED THESE DATA?Eosta/Nature&More processes your personal data in order to be able to contact you by telephone if you request this, and/or to be able to contact you in writing (by e-mail and/or by post) if you cannot be reached by telephone.In addition, Eosta/Nature&More may use your personal data in the context of the execution of an agreement concluded with you, usually consisting of services.HOW LONG DO WE STORE YOUR DATA?Eosta/Nature&More does not store your personal data for longer than strictly necessary to achieve the purposes for which your data are collected. Your data will be stored for up to two years when no agreement is concluded with you.SHARING WITH OTHERSEosta/Nature&More only provides your personal data to third parties if this is necessary for the execution of an agreement with you, or in order to comply with a legal obligation.MAPPING OUR WEBSITE VISITSOn the Eosta/Nature&More website, we track general visitor data, including your computer's IP address and the time of retrieval and data sent by your browser. These data are used for analyses of visitor and click behaviour on the website. Eosta/Nature&More uses this information to improve the way the website works. This information will be made as anonymous as possible and will not be provided to third parties.GOOGLE ANALYTICSEosta/Nature&More uses Google Analytics to track how users use the website and the effectiveness of Eosta/Nature&More Adwords ads on Google search result pages. The information obtained in this way, including the address of your computer (IP address), will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Please read Google's privacy policy for more information. You will also find the privacy policy of Google Analytics here. Google will use this information to track how our site is used, to compile reports on the website for Eosta/Nature&More and provide its advertisers with information about the effectiveness of their campaigns. Google may also transfer this information to third parties if required to do so by law, or when such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Eosta/Nature&More has no influence on this. Eosta/Nature&More has not authorised Google to use Analytics information obtained from Eosta/Nature&More for any other Google service.ACCESS, CORRECT, DELETE YOUR DATAYou have the right to access, correct or delete your personal data. You can send a request for inspection, correction or deletion to michiel@eosta.com. Eosta/Nature&More will respond to your request as soon as possible, within four weeks at the latest.PROTECTIONEosta/Nature&More takes the protection of your data very seriously and takes appropriate measures to prevent misuse, loss, unauthorised access, unwanted disclosure and unauthorised alteration. The Eosta/Nature&More website uses a reliable SSL Certificate to ensure that your personal data do not fall into the wrong hands. If you have the impression that your data are not secure, or if there are indications of misuse, or if you would like more information about the protection of personal data collected by Eosta/Nature&More, please contact Eosta/Nature&More via michiel@eosta.com.www.natureandmore.com and www.eosta.com are websites of Eosta/Nature&More. Eosta/Nature&More can be reached as follows:Postal address: PO Box 348, 2740 AH Waddinxveen, NetherlandsOffice address: Transportweg 7, 2742 RH Waddinxveen, NetherlandsChamber of Commerce registration number: 30135547Telephone: +31(0)180 635 500E-mail address: info[at]eosta.com
SHARE
You are hereHome
The Sustainability FlowerThe Sustainability Flower is the core of our business. Every Nature & More grower has a personal Sustainability Flower. It points the way to a greener and more social economy. More info here.
Contact
T +31 (0)180 63 55 00F +31 (0)180 89 03 98info@eosta.comwww.eosta.com
